穿过雪
Through the snow and sleet and hail...
穿过大风雪
through the blizzard, through the gale...
穿过阵阵强风和暴雨
through the wind and through the rain...
穿过山 穿过平原
over mountain, over plain...
穿过刺眼的闪电光!
through the blinding lightning flash...
穿过巨大的闪电!
and the mighty thunder crash...
曾经一切平静! 曾经一切流畅
ever faithful, ever true...
无法阻止它…你曾经历到的
nothing stops him.
雨很快就要停了
He'll get through.
看着鹳先生 那个执着的家伙
Look out for Mr.Stork that persevering chap
与风雨抗争 它的喙上挂了个婴儿袋
He'll come along and drop a bundle in your lap
不管你是穷人还是富人
You may be poor or rich it doesn't matter which
它不管你是不是百万富翁 不管你是屠夫还是烤面包的
Millionaires, they get theirs like the butcher and the baker
这些它都不在意 我们的鹳先生 朋友 让我来告诉你吧
So look out for Mr.Stork and let me tell you, friend
不要想着抛弃它 他最后还是会找到你
Don't try to get away He'll find you in the end
他将从陶罐里把你揪出来 或者从地方法庭找到你
He'll spot you out in China or he'll fly to County Cork
所以你最好老实点 迎接小生命
So you'd better look out for Mr.Stork
看着鹳先生 它已经把你记住了
Look out for Mr.Stork He's got you on his list
它一旦开始了 拒绝它是徒劳的
And when he comes around it's useless to resist
还记得那些不育的女人吗?
Remember those quintuplets and the woman in the shoe
说不定她正在白眼看你
Maybe he's got his eye on you
全都上车了!
All aboard! All aboard!
全都上车了! 我们走吧
All aboard! Let's go!
忙碌的小火车在铁轨上
Casey Junior's comin' down the track
在铁轨上飞驰 穿过阻碍烟雾的隧道
Comin' down the track with a smoky stack
听听它蜿蜒绕过小山的声音
Hear him puffiin' comin' round the hill
男人和女人都在为它发抖
Casey's here to thrill every Jack and Jill
它总是在喘气 伴随着时不时的启笛声
Every time his funny little whistle sounds
每个人都很困乏
Everybody hurries to the circus grounds
在车上喝柠檬水 吃饼干打发时间
Time for lemonade and Cracker Jack
远去的小火车 远去的小火车
Casey Junior's back Casey Junior's back
哦 好累哦!
Oh. My, my.
我看看啊
Now let me see.
应该就是附近这个地方
Must be right around here somewhere.
我希望是 我再查查看
I hope. Ah, watch it there.
“在树梢上”
“On the treetop”
这是哪里了?
Where are we here? Oh, here.
我们在61号高速公路的上面离加油站4英里
Highway 61, four miles to the gas station
左转弯
Turn left Da-da da-da-da de
喔…就是它了
Ah. That must be it.
好了 小家伙! 我们出发吧!
Well, little fella, let's get goin'.
Mrs.Jumbo. Oh, Mrs.Jumbo.
叫 Mrs.Jumbo.
Calling Mrs.Jumbo.
Mrs.Jumbo?
哦  天
Oh. My.
Mrs.Jumbo!
Mrs.Jumbo 你到底在哪里?
- Oh, where's that Mrs.Jum...
- 在这儿啊… - 来…
- Over here. - This way, boy.
- 这里! 这里! - 哟呵!
- In here! In here! - Yoo-hoo!
- 原来在这里啊 - 在这里
- This is the place. - Whew! At last.
哪一位女士正在等啊?
Which one of you ladies is expecting?
- 哦 不是我!  - 这样套近乎?
- Hmph! Not me. - The very idea.
也不是我!  是在角落里那边的那一位
Certainly not. Over there, of course.
是的 当然
Yes, of course. Right over there.
当然!
Oh. Of course.
这个蓝色眼睛小婴儿...
Here is a baby with eyes of blue...
是直接从天堂送来给你的
straight from heaven right to you.
直接从上面天堂送来给你的...
Or: Straight from heaven up above...
请你用爱心好好的爱他
here is a baby for you to love.
请签名!
Sign here, please.
好的! Mrs.Jumbo
Uh, yeah. Well... Oh. Mrs.Jumbo.
请等一下 好不好? 这也是服务的一部分
Uh, one moment, please. This is still part of the service.
祝你生日快乐
Happy Birthday to you
Ah, Happy Birthday to you
祝你生日快乐
Ah, Happy Birthday, dear
祝你生…他叫什么名字啊?
Ah, dear Dear me. What's his name?
Jumbo.Junior.
Oh! Jumbo Junior, huh? Ahem! Jumbo Junior.
祝Jumbo.Junior生日快乐
Happy Birthday, dear Jumbo Junior
祝你生日快乐
Happy Birthday To-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo-oo You
- 我迫不及待要看了 - 真是幸福啊
- Oh, do hurry, dear. - I'm on pins and needles.
- 一定很可爱? - 我也很想看看
- Isn't it thrilling? - I'm all a-flutter.
真是个伟大的日子啊
Ah, this is a proud, proud day.
- 赶快打开来看看啊 - 我等着要看呢
- Well, hurry and open it, dearie. - I'm just dying to see.
- 哦 - 你看看他!
- Oh! - Look at him!
你看看他!
Look at him!
看看!
Oh, what a... Oh, look!
- 这么可爱的小东西 - 真可爱啊
- Oh, you sweet little thing. - He is cute, isn't he?
哦  可爱的小宝宝
Oh, he is a darling little baby.
真可爱，小可爱
Adorable. Simply adorable.
你们有看过这么可爱的东西吗?
Did you ever see anything so cunning?
它好可爱哟!
Isn't he a darling!
- 这是不可能的啊? - 是不是有什么错误啊?
- Is it possible? - Isn't there some mistake?
看这里
Just look at those, those...
耳  朵
E-A-R-S.
耳朵怎么了?
Those what? Oh, ears!
你看看她的耳朵长得好奇怪啊
These! Aren't they funny? Oh!
- 哦 天 - 真气人呀
- Oh, my goodness. - What a temper.
我做了什么吗?
Oh, what did I do? Well, tell me.
- 我说了什么? - 这完全是没有伤害的啊
- Did I say anything? - Perfectly harmless remark.
我只是觉得很好笑而已啊
I just said that they're funny, and they are funny.
- 本来就是嘛! - 反正谁在乎...
- They certainly are. - After all, who cares...
她的小Jumbo啊?
about her precious little Jumbo?
Jumbo?你是说Dumbo吧!
Jumbo? You mean Dumbo.
Dumbo.
- 我说 Dumbo - 很好
- Dumbo, I say. - That's good.
- Dumbo! 很好 - Dumbo
- Dumbo! That's good. - Dumbo.
我一定能爬上去 我一定能爬上去
I think I can. I think I can. I think I can. I think I can.
I think I can. I think I can. I think I can.
我就说我能爬上来嘛
I thought I could.
我们整天整夜地工作
We work all day We work all night
We never learned to read or write
We're happy-hearted roustabouts
Hike, ugh, hike, ugh hike, ugh, hike
When other folks have gone to bed
We slave until we're almost dead
We're happy-hearted roustabouts
Hike, ugh, hike, ugh hike, ugh, hike
We don't know when we get our pay
And when we do we throw our pay away
When we get our pay we throw our money all away
We get our pay when children say
With happy hearts It's circus day today
Then we get our pay just watching kids on circus day
Muscles aching Back near breaking
Eggs and bacon's what we need
- Yes, sir! - Boss man houndin'
Keep on poundin'
For your bread and keep
There ain't no letup
Got to set up
Pull that canvas
Drive that stake
Want to doze off Get them clothes off
But must keep awake
Hep! Heave! Hep! Heave! Hep! Heave! Hep! Heave!
Hep! Heave! Hep! Heave! Hep! Heave! Hep!
Swing that sledge Sing that song
Work and laugh the whole night long
You happy-hearted roustabouts
Pullin: poundin' tyin: groundin'
Big top roundin' into shape
Keep on workin' Stop that shirkin'
Grab that rope, you hairy ape
Poundin: poundin'
马戏表演了，还有15分钟
Jostling and juggling. Fifteen minutes!
欢迎各位买票进来参观啊，快点啊
Step right up and get your tickets. Hurry, hurry now.
各位先生! 来看最顶尖的表演啊!
Hurry to the big sideshow. That's why you go under the big top.
在全世界别的地方看不见的
Fifteen big attractions that you can't see anywhere else in the world!
有各式各样奇怪
The greatest collection in the entire world.
以及最伟大的动物明星啊
And the greatest comedies are featured and assembled for your entertainment.
难道你不认为这些是你从未见过最有趣的? 看看它的耳朵
Ain't that the funniest thing you ever saw? Look at his ears.
嘿 快看 一只象
Hey, guys, look it! Smitty's an elephant!
- 让我看看 - 啵!
- Aw, let me see! - Boo!
- 象妈妈把它藏起来了 - 它不出来了
- You can't hide him from us. - Yeah, his ears are still stickin' out.
我们要看
- Come on! - We wanna see him!
- 我们要看哪 - 我们来这就是为了看这个的
- We wanna laugh. - Sure, that's what we came for.
世界上最大的弹弓
Hey, the biggest slingshot in the world.
我抓到你了
Hey! Cut that out! Hey, let's get out of here.
怎么回事啊?
You're hurting me! Help! Here, you! What's going on?
停止! Mrs.Jumbo
Down. Mrs.Jumbo, down!
当心她
Surround her. Tie her down.
当心
Get down!
安静下来! 带她出去
Calm down! Tie her down!
'疯狂大象'   '小心! '
Darling, it was so funny.
真有意思! 你能拍它吗?
Oh, my dear, can you bear it?
它小的时候 我还以为它会死掉呢
When she doused the ringmaster, I just thought I'd die.
好了 大伙 我想她做的大过份了
Well, personally, I think she went a bit too far.
不管怎么样我们都该保持淑女形象啊
After all, one mustn't forget one is a lady.
- 你说的对 亲爱的 - 非常对
- Oh, you're right, dear. Yes. - Oh, that's very true.
不过我想那是出于母爱吧
Oh, well, I suppose that's mother love.
但是也不能当做胡来的藉口啊
But it's certainly no excuse for what she did.
也许母爱让她冲昏了头啦!
Mother love might cover a multitude of sins.
女孩们 听着! 我不想吃东西时
It's true, my dear, and she has such a streak in...
过于宁静
A guy can't eat in peace.
是的 但是妈妈喜欢...
Yes, but mother love does...
总是在闲聊
Gab, gab, gab. Always gossipin'.
女孩们 听着!
Girls, girls! Listen!
如果我有个像他这样的儿子啊
Have I got a trunk full of dirt.
- 继续说啊 - 继续
- Well, darling, tell us all. - Go on, go on.
我今天听说啊 主人将她监禁了
Well, I heard today that they have put her in solitary confinement.
- 哦 不  - 你不是那个意思!
- No! - You don't mean it!
好可怕的事啊!
Oh, how awful for her!
那么我要说啊 任何事情我都不会怪她的
Well, I-I must say, I-I don't blame her for anything.
完全正确! 都是那个小怪物的错...
You're absolutely right. It's all the fault of that little...
都是他那对鬼-耳-朵
F-R-E-A-K.
就是嘛! 那对鬼耳朵只有他妈才会喜欢哪
Yes, him with those ears that only a mother could love.
他耳朵没有什么不好啊
What's the matter with his ears
我看不出有什么不好的 我觉得很可爱耶
I don't see nothin' wrong with 'em. I think they're cute.
女士们 女士们! 这一点也不好笑
Ladies, ladies! It's no laughing matter at all.
哦 她是对的
Oh. Oh, she's right, girls.
别忘了我们大象连走路都带着尊严哪
Don't forget that we elephants have always walked with dignity.
那个耳朵使我们觉得丢脸
His disgrace is our own shame.
- 说的对 - 当然是
- Yes, that's true. That's very true. - Oh, indeed it is.
坦白说 我不愿意跟他吃同样的干草了
Well, frankly, I wouldn't eat at the same bale of hay with him.
我也不…我也不愿意
No. Right.Me either, dearie.
我也有这种感觉
I should say.Nor I. That's just how I feel about it.
它走过来了
Here he comes now.
我们假装没看到它
Hmm. Pretend you don't see him.
你喜欢这样吗? 每只象都那么冷淡这小家伙好可怜喔
How do ya like that? Givin' him the cold shoulder.
可怜的小家伙
Poor little guy.
它失望的走了 它没有朋友
There he goes, without a friend in the world.
也没有人可以依赖
Nobody to turn to.
我一定要为他尽点力才行
Oh, I'll do somethin' about this.
一只老鼠
A mouse!
你们喜欢欺负小东西 是不是?
So ya like to pick on little guys, huh?
你们来找我啊
Well, why don't you pick on me?
你们以为你们的血统很优越吗?
A proud race.
可是你们却没有种!
Overstuffed hay bags!
居然怕一支小老鼠
Still afraid of a mouse.
我要去告诉那小家伙
Ho-ho, boy. Wait'll I tell the little guy.
你在哪里啊? Dumbo
Where is he? Oh. Hey, Dumbo.
可以出来了
You can come out now.
是不是我吓到你了 Dumbo?
Golly. Maybe I scared him too.
你出来嘛! 我是你的朋友哦
Look, Dumbo. I'm your friend.
快点出来啊 好吗?
Come on out, won't ya?
你不会连我这么小你都害怕吧?
You're not really afraid of little me, are ya?
你会害怕我? 是
Ya are? Must've overdid it in there.
我不是那个意思 我只是有时有点奇怪而已
Don't know my own strength sometimes.
Dumbo 看我给你带来什么了
Dumbo. Look what I got for ya.
你要先出来才行啊 Dumbo
Uh-uh-uh-uh. Ya gotta come out first.
我知道也许你不信赖我
Too bad ya don't trust me, 'cause I thought...
除了你我 你要考虑考虑你妈呀
uh, well, you... you and me, uh, we might get your mother out of the clink.
我猜你没兴趣吧
Oh, but I guess you wouldn't be interested. So long, Dumbo.
那我只好走 再见了 Dumbo!
Well, that's more like it.
你知道 你妈妈并不是真疯狂
Ya know, your ma ain't crazy.
她只是为你操碎了心
She's just brokenhearted.
没有人能够不为你的耳朵而烦恼的
It ain't nobody's fault you got them big ears.
老天啊! 我不该这样说你的 对不对?
Uh-oh. Boy, I stepped in it that time.
你快乐一点嘛 Dumbo 我觉得你的耳朵还是很漂亮的
Aw, gee, Dumbo. I think your ears are beautiful.
当然啦 事实上我觉得你又灵巧又可爱
Sure. As a matter of fact, I think they're very decorative.
有很多大耳朵的人都很有名
You know, lots of people with big ears are famous.
老弟 我们最重要的是要有个特色 对不对?
Ho-ho, boy. All we gotta do is build an act.
要做一个大明星
Make ya a star. A headliner!
头号大明星 Dumbo
Dumbo the Great!
最伟大的?
Uh-oh. The great what?
你知道吗 Dumbo 我们有个好主意
Ya know, Dumbo, we gotta get an idea.
可不是普通的主意哦 是特别的主意
Not just any idea. Something colossal, like, uh...
我有个好主意
Have I got an idea! What an idea!
他们是不会有好主意的
Huh. He never had an idea in his life.
想象一下 我需要有一支大象
Just visualize: One elephant climbs up...
爬到其它大象顶上去
on top of another elephant until finally...
直到最后十七支大象
all 17 elephants...
排成一个出色的队形
have constructed an enormous pyramid...
金字塔形
of pachyderms.
这个时候我站出来
I step out.
吹哨子
I blow the whistle.
- 耶 - 号声和鼓声齐奏
- Yeah. - The trumpets are trumpeting.
- 耶 - 然后我们的节目
- Yeah. - And now...
就出现高潮了!
comes the climax!
什么是高…高潮啊?
Yeah? What is the climax?
我还不知道呢
Hmm. I don't know.
我就知道他想不出来
I knew he never had nothin'.
也许当我睡著的时候
Well, maybe it comes to me...
我就会想到了
in a vision while I dream.
- Good night, Joe. - Good night, Boss.
高潮!
Climax.
高潮! Dumbo 你就是那个高潮!
Climax! Dumbo, you're a climax.
我一会就回来 我会负责你的前途的
I'll be back in a minute. I'm gonna take care of your future.
我是你的潜意识
I am the voice of your subconscious mind.
和你的灵感
Your inspiration.
现在要集中注意力了
Now, concentrate.
记得你的那群大象
Remember? Your pyramid of elephants...
要排成金字塔状
are standing in the ring waitin' for a climax.
- 高潮 - 现在我告诉你什么是节目高潮!
- Climax. - You are now getting that climax.
- 高潮 - 什么?
- Climax. - How's the reception?
不错 就是现在
Comin' through okay? Good.
好! 突然从一片静寂之中出现高潮了
Suddenly, from the sidelines, comes your climax.
- 高潮 - 快速跑过舞台
- Climax. - Gallopin' across the arena.
他一路跑过滑扳道
Arena.He jumps from a springboard...to a platform.
他升上舞台了 在整个大象堆中最高点 他摇着旗子
At the very pinnacle of your pyramid, he waves a flag...
光辉的结束
for a glorious finish!
- 结束? - 谁来完成你的高潮戏呢?
- Finish? - And who is your climax?
有大耳朵的小象!
The little elephant with the big ears!
最矮的…Dumbo
The world's mightiest midget mastodon! Dumbo!
什么?
What?
- Dumbo - Dumbo
有了 有了!
I got it! I got it!
女士们 先生们...
Ladies and gentlemen...
我们很荣幸为各位介绍...
we will now present for your entertainment...
一个最伟大壮观的
the most stupendous, magnificent...
本世纪最棒的表演
super-colossal spectacle.
在这个微小...
On this tiny...
而不足道的球上面...
little, insignificant ball...
大象们要堆成一个金字塔的形状
we will construct for you...
这可不是开玩笑的
a pyramid, not of wood, not of stone...
听到没啊 他还以为我们会这招呢
To hear him talk, you'd think he was going to do it.
哦 快停下
but a living, breathing...The stuffed shirt.
给你象
I give you the elephants.
你们两个笨手笨脚的
Aren't we a bit clumsy?
请你不要压我好不好啊 亲爱的?
Gaining a little weight, aren't you, honey?
你知道我也是没有办法的呀
You're no cream puff yourself, dearie.
安静一点 专心工作
Quiet up there. Tend to your work, girls.
你的大脚不要蒙住我的眼睛上 大白鲨
Take your foot out of my eye, clumsy ox.
站稳啊 姑娘们
Steady, girls.
老弟啊 马上该你了
Boy, that was a close one.
你要准备好 Dumbo! 用力摇旗子
They're almost ready now, Dumbo. Don't forget to wave that flag.
好了好了 不要摇那么用力 我看着你
Okay, okay. Don't wave it no more. I saw ya.
现在 看好了 待会儿要跑出去
Now, look. All ya gotta do is run out, see?
然后跳上舞台
Jump on the springboard.
好 让我看看你要怎么做
All right, now show me just how you're gonna do it.
对了 老弟向前跑
That's it. Attaboy. That's the stuff. Come on.
哦... 向前跑 Dumbo
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! Dumbo!
都是你的大耳朵 我们一定要把它处理掉
Oh, those ears. We gotta do somethin', quick.
女士们 先生们...
Ladies and gentlemen...
现在你们将要看到...
you have now seen the impossible...
一幕不可思议的秀
accomplished in front of your faces.
大象们要展现
Seven jungle giants...
她们的柔力了
each one weighing not...
那个老家伙废话一大堆
That windbag!
- 最下面重量是多少啊? - 7500磅!
- Why doesn't he come to the point? - 7,500 pounds!
现在
And now, I present...
我要介绍是世界上最小的大象了
the world's smallest little elephant...
它将要通过跳台...
who will spring from this springboard...
然后一下子跳到大象群的最高平台上面
to the top of this pyramid, waving his little flag...
在上面摇动旗子进入这个节目的最高潮!
for a grand climax!
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
现在我要向你们介绍Dumbo!
I give you Dumbo!
走啊…Dumbo!
Go on! Get goin'!
你怎么回事嘛? 快走 你快上场!
What's the matter with you? Dumbo! That's your cue!
你能行的 Dumbo
You're on, Dumbo.
快走开啊 你这个惹事专家
Out of my way, assassin!
- 天! - 哦
- Dear! - Ohh.
我真不敢想像我亲眼看到这一幕
I never thought I'd live to see the big top fall.
都是Dumbo 我的脸也不能见人了
Because of that Dumbo, I never can show my face there again.
看看我漂亮的尾巴!
Oh, look at my beautiful tail!
我只想痛打这个小家伙一顿...
I'd just like to spank the daylights out of him...
哦  这个不急 亲爱的
Oh, that won't be necessary, dearie.
马戏团的人会处理的
They fixed him good.
- 你是什么意思? - 他们会怎么做?
- What do you mean? - Wh-What did they do?
- 他们打他了吗? - 有这事吗 亲爱的?
- Did they beat him? - What is it, darling?
- 告诉我们! - 快 我需要知道
- Tell us. - Come, come. I demand to know.
哦  他们把他
Oh. Well, they've gone and made him...
- 亲爱的 我不能说 - 赶走了?
- Oh, dear, I just can't say it. - Out with it!
把他当成小丑
Made him a clown.
小丑?
A clown?
- 不! - 是的
- No! - Yes.
哦 它真是可耻啊
Oh, the shame of it.
让我们为它立誓吧
Let us take the solemn vow.
从现在开始 他不再是头
From now on, he is no longer...
大象了
an elephant.
快救救我可怜的孩子啊!
Please! Help me save my poor baby!
救命! 快点救救它啊!
Whoo! Save my child!
嘿...你在哪里? 哟呵!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Where are you? Yoo-hoo!
救我的孩子
Save my ba...
- 快 跳 快点! - 孩子 我们是不是太野蛮了?
- Come on! Jump! - We'll save you. Hurry up!
- 赶紧! - 我们来救你
- Hurry up! - We'll save you. Go on.
- 跳! - 我们来救你
-Jump! - We'll save ya.
孩子 我们把你救出去
Whew! Boy, oh, boy, did we wow 'em out there!
- 你看我表演得好啊 - 好吗?
- What a performance! - Are we good?
十三次
Thirteen curtain calls. Thirteen!
是的 把它收拾了
Yeah, sure brought down the house, all right.
哦  妈妈 我们难道不棒吗?
Oh, Mama, did we panic 'em. Ask me, Joey. Go ahead. Ask me.
你闭嘴 我们让它们在地上翻滚
You said it. We rolled 'em in the aisles.
- 真是太棒了 - 多棒的表演呀!
- Boy, oh, boy, what an act. - Oh, "what an act" is right.
辉煌极了 我喜欢这样说
Stupendous, I call it.
他们因为我们这些小丑(的出色表演)而得到了更多的尊重
They'll have more respect for us clowns now.
- 是的 你打赌 - 这里 孩子
- Yeah, yeah, you bet. - Here, boys.
这次是真的为了庆祝 来吧
This calls for a real celebration. Come and get it.
- 我有点口渴了 - 我自己来吧!
- Poison! Am I thirsty. - I could use one of them myself.
- 这是给Dumbo的 - 嗯 Dumbo
- This one's on Dumbo. - Yeah, Dumbo.
- Dumbo! - 在他眼里
- Dumbo! - Here's plaster in his eyes.
听到没? 他们在敬你
See? They're drinkin' a toast to ya.
你表演得非常非常的卖座
Yeah. You're a big hit.
你极受欢迎
Why, uh, you're terrific.
哦  你是非凡的
Oh, you're colossal. Stupendous.
来 带我上去我帮你擦耳朵啊
Come on. Alley-oop. I gotta wash behind your ears.
你应该感到自豪!
You ought a be proud.
你一定会红
You're a success.
你看 这是花生!
Look. A peanut!
快点吃下去 它有丰富的维他命
Come on. Eat it. Got lots of vitamins.
丰富的
Give ya a lot of, uh, pep.
啊 我忘了告诉你一件事
Oh-ho-ho. I forgot to tell ya.
我们要去看你的妈妈哦
Why, we're goin' over to see your mother.
而且啊 我们帮你约好了
I made an appointment for ya. Didn't I tell ya? Huh!
只是我忘记告诉你而已 来 把帽子戴上
Just like me. I must have forgot. Come on. Get your hat.
就在那里啊
Oh. Right over there.
小小的安乐窝 不是吗?
Cozy little place, ain't it?
Mrs.Jumbo 我想她在里边
Mrs.Jumbo. I hope she's in.
有人要来看你了
Someone to see ya.
我的孩子
Baby mine
不要哭
Don't you cry
我的孩子
Baby mine
来来来 躺在我身边
Dry your eyes
把你的头
Rest your head
靠在我的胸前
Close to my heart
不要走远
Never to part
你是我的孩子
Baby of mine
小小的一个宝贝
Little one
表演时
When you play
不要在意
Don't you mind
他们说的话啊
What they say
让他们去
Let those eyes
出风头吧
Sparkle and shine
一滴泪都不要哭
Never a tear
你是我的孩子
Baby of mine
从头到脚
From your head to your toes
我的孩子
Baby mine
你是那么的甜蜜 全身洋溢着欢乐
You're so sweet goodness knows
我的孩子
Baby mine
- 你是... - 宝贝...
- You are so - Baby, baby, baby
- 我的珍爱 - 我的
- Precious to me - Mine
你是我的孩子
Cute as can be baby of mine
我的孩子
Baby mine
给 倒到我鞋上 Joey
Here ya are. Pour it in me slipper, Joey.
我不能赶它们在通道上打滚
Boy, I can't get over the way we rolled 'em in the aisles.
- 就象我们堆象一样 - 从这件事中 我有个主意
- Just wait'll we hit the big town. - This gives me an idea.
我们升高舞台 让象从上面跳下来
Let's raise the platform the elephant jumps off of.
是的 如果大象跳下20英尺 观众会很高兴...
Yeah! If they laugh when he jumps 20 feet...
如果它跳40英尺 大伙会更高兴
they'll laugh twice as hard if he jumps 40 feet.
- 完全正确 - 这是个简单的数学运算
- Yeah, that's right. That's right. - Simple mathematics.
- 我们要做到80英尺 - 不要怕 180英尺
- Let's make it 80 feet. - Don't be a piker. 180.
- 甚至三百 - 一千
- Make it 300. - A thousand.
- 对 - 这样才好
- Yeah, that's good. - Hey, be careful.
- 当然小心不要把大象给弄伤啦 - 继续
- You'll hurt the little guy. - Aw, go on.
- 不会啦! 大象根本没有感觉 - 是 它们是橡胶做的
- Elephants ain't got no feelings. - No, they're made of rubber.
这主意蛮好的 那我们去跟老板说好不好?
This idea is sensational. Let's go tell the boss.
- 嗯 嗯 嗯 - 走 我们走
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Come on. Let's go.
嗨 我们升高它
Hey, hey! Let's hit him for a raise.
是的 当然 这可是实在的金子
Yeah, sure. This is worth real dough.
我们要让大老板加多报酬
Oh, we're gonna hit the big boss for a raise
是的 我们要让大老板加多报酬
Yes, we're gonna hit the big boss for a raise
哦 我们要让大老板加多报酬 因为我们确实会搞笑
Oh, we're gonna get more money 'cause we know that we're funny
我们要让大老板加多报酬
We're gonna hit the big boss for a raise
Dumbo 缩紧你的身躯
I know how ya feel, Dumbo, but you gotta pull yourself together.
如果你妈妈看到你哭成这个样子的话 她一定很难过
What would your mother think of ya, if she saw you crying like this?
记住 你来自光荣的血统
Remember, you come of a proud race.
你是高贵的象
Why you're a-a-a... a pachyderm...
高贵的象是不会哭的哦
and pachyderms don't cry.
哭又有什么用呢 对不对? 它只会让你打嗝
What's cryin' get ya anyhow? Nothin' but the hiccups.
看那里
There. Ya see?
对了 好像水可以治疗哭
Well, ain't nothin' a little water won't cure.
我们是一流的 我们让你马上恢复
Oops-a-daisy. We'll have ya fixed up in a jiffy.
来吧!
Come on.
来 喝一口!
Here. Take a trunk full.
听着 伙伴!
Listen, little fella.
我们到现在还不是很走运
We may have had a lot of hard luck up till now...
但是 我想我们一定会做大事[成功]的
but you and me is gonna do big things together.
屏住呼吸 你妈妈也一定会以你为荣
Hold your breath. Why, your mother's gonna be so proud of ya.
我也会以你为荣
I'm gonna be proud of ya too.
整个马戏团都会以你为荣 你以为如何?
The whole circus is gonna be proud of ya. Now, what do ya think of that?
吞下去
Swallow it.
哦  他们不会再看不起你了
Ho-ho. They can't keep us down.
我想大概你肚子有点饿吧
Oh, I guess you had one little one left over.
Dumbo 我们一定会成功
Dumbo, we'll bounce back so ha...
嘿 你到底怎么回事啊?
Hey, what's the matter with you?
这到底是什么水啊?
What kind of water is this, anyhow?
哦 气球!
Balloonies.
我喜欢
Hiya, George.
我们 我们
Whee!
多么漂亮又光滑
That's a pretty schstrick schlick.
好了 让我们来吹个正方体怎么样啊?
All right. Let's see ya blow a square one, pal.
你很聪明嘛!
Say, that's very, very clever.
现在我们来吹个特大号
Now blow a great big one.
这个形状真不错
That's a pretty sh... Hey!
Dumbo.
你看到没?
You see what I see?
快看 快看 大象在游行
Look out, look out Pink elephants on parade
它们来了
Here they come Hippity-hoppity
到处都是大象
They're here and there Pink elephants everywhere
快看 快看
Look out, look out
大象在马戏团周围走来走去
They're walking around the bed on their head
到处都是
Clippity-cloppity Arrayed in braid
勇敢些 大象
Pink elephants on parade
- 我做什么呢? - 我做什么呢?
- What'll I do - What'll I do
多么不同寻常的想法!
What an unusual view
我可看到虫 看到了细菌
I can stand the sight of worms and look at microscopic germs
这些东西对我而言还是太多了
But Technicolor pachyderms is really too much for me
我可不是
I am not the type to faint
以貌取人的那种人
When things are odd or things are quaint
所见的不一定是真的
But seein' things you know there ain't
说不定给你一个巨大的惊奇
Can certainly give you an awful fright
多奇妙的景观! 追上它们
What a sight Chase 'em away, chase 'em away
我害怕 我需要你的帮助
I'm afraid, need your aid Pink elephants on parade
- 嘿 - 大象
- Hey, hey, hey - Pink elephants
大象
Pink elephants
- 你看那里… - 我的天哪!
- Well, looky here, looky here. - My, my.
这真是不寻常的事…
Why, this is most irregular.
我真是不敢相信我的眼睛
Well, I just can't believe my eyes.
- 他们死了吗? - 死人是不会打鼾的
- They ain't dead, is they? - No. Dead people don't snore.Or do they?
你们在干什么啊?
Uh, wh-what's all the ruckus? Come on.
站到一边去 兄弟们 煮了什么吃呢?
Step aside, brother. Uh, what's cookin' 'round here?
有好消息吗? 哪来的好消息?
What's the good news? What's fryin', boy?
- 看看下边! - 小心不要震惊得摔跤!
- Just look down there, brother. - And prepare yourself for a shock.
- 我的脚呢? - 去 叫醒他
- Well, hush my beak! - Go ahead. Wake 'em up, brother.
去看看他们在上面做什么?
Yeah. Find out what they're doin' up here.
- 好 - 问问他们想要什么
- Yeah. - And "ax" them what they want.
好的 这件事情让我来好了
Okay, boys. Leave it to me.
大象嘛!
Ohh! Those pink elephants.
哦  大象?
Ho! Pink elephants? Mm-mmm!
这有什么好笑的 你们这些孩子在下面作什么?
What's so funny? What are you boys doin' down here, anyway?
我们在下面干什么啊?
What are we doin' down here?
有没有听到他说话?
Well, hear him talk.
飞到树上去
Go on. Fly up a tree where you belong.
- 老鼠兄弟! - 老鼠兄弟?
- Say, look here, Brother Rat. - Brother Rat?
听着 我不是你的兄弟 我也不是老鼠
Now listen. I ain't your brother and I ain't no rat, see?
我认为任何一支大象
Uh-huh. And I suppose you...
都不会爬树
and no elephant ain't up in no tree, either.
哦  不 我在树上?
No! No, me and no tree ain't up no... Huh?
树上?
Tree?
Dumbo.
Dumbo. Wake up.
Wake up, Dumbo!
别往下看! 我们好像确实在树上
Don't look now, but I think we're up in a tree.
不要管那些混蛋 我们走吧
Aw, don't pay no attention to them scarecrows.
Dumbo 我们回马戏团去!
Come on, Dumbo. Let's get back to the circus.
再见了!
So long, boy!
我真想不通我们怎么会在树上
But I wonder how we ever got up in that tree, anyway.
我想想看啊
Now, let's see.
大象是不会爬树的 对吧?
Elephants can't climb trees, can they?
不  不  不 太荒谬了!
Nah, nah, that's ridiculous.
是我们爬上去的?那也太高(太难)了
Couldn't jump up. Mm-mm. It's too high.
用飞的! 也许你们是飞上去的
Hey there, son. Maybe you all flew up.
飞上去?  对呀! 我们是飞上去的
Maybe we flew up. Yeah, maybe we...
对啦 Dumbo 你可以飞了
That's it! Dumbo! You flew!
我真笨 怎么以前从没这样想过呢?
Boy, am I stupid. Why didn't I think of this before?
用你的大耳朵 Dumbo 你看你的耳朵 它们是最好的翅膀呀!
Your ears. Just look at 'em, Dumbo. Why, they're perfect wings.
这特别的天赋让你飞的! 它会让你飞得很高 很高 很高
The very things that held ya down are gonna carry ya up and up and up!
我都已经可以想像到那种情形了
I can see it all now.
Dumbo 你是世界上的第九大奇迹!
Dumbo, the Ninth Wonder of the Universe!
全世界唯一会飞的大象!
The world's only flyin' elephant!
你以前看过会飞的大象吗?
Did you ever see an elephant fly?
- 我看过马会飞啊 - 我看过龙会飞
- Well, I've seen a horsefly. - Ah, I've seen a dragonfly.
- 我看过房子会飞啊 - 嗯!
- Hee-hee. I've seen a housefly. - Yeah!
我也看过…
See, I've seen all that too.
我看过花生跳舞 我听过一大群人的乐队
I've seen a peanut stand and heard a rubber band.
我看过针眨眼呢
I seen a needle that winked its eye.
这些都不足以让我惊讶
But I be done seen about ever'thing
至到我看见大象在飞
When I see a elephant fly
- 你们在说什么? - 我说至到我看到大象在飞
- What'd you say, boy? - I said when I see a elephant fly
我看到过门摇晃 听过钻戒的声音
I seen a front porch swing heard a diamond ring
我见过弯曲的铁轨
I seen a polka-dot railroad tie
但这些都不足为奇
But I be done seen 'bout ever'thing
至到我见到大象在飞
When I see a elephant fly
我在一本关于大象的书上见过与这接近的现象
I saw a clotheshorse He rear up and buck
我还听说用蔬菜茎作的人
And they tell me that a man made a vegetable truck
我只是听说 没亲自见过
I didn't see that I only heard
我会提供你第一手资料的
Just to be sociable I'll take your word
- 我听说一辆车聊天呢 - 我看见棒球拍
- I heard a fireside chat - I saw a baseball bat
我会为此而笑到死
And I just laughed till I thought I'd die
我不会对这些惊讶
But I be done seen 'bout ever'thing
至到我见到会飞的大象
When I see a elephant fly
我不会对这些惊讶
But I be done seen 'bout ever'thing
至到我见到会飞的大象
When I see a elephant fly
有翅膀的大象
With the wind.
当我听到大象会
When I see a elephant
飞
Fly
好啦 你们这些家伙实在是大过分了
All right, you wise birds. This has gone far enough.
先生们 安静啊!
Quiet, gentlemen.
让我来说说
The Reverend Rodent is gonna address you.
你应该要觉得惭愧才对的
You ought a be ashamed of yourselves.
你这么的大个子怎么可以欺负这个小可怜虫!
A bunch of big guys like you...
想象一下你刚出生就和母亲分离了
pickin' on a poor little orphan like him.
那时你只是个小宝宝...
Suppose you was torn away from your mother when you was just a baby...
晚上没有人喂你...
nobody to tuck you in at nights...
也没有温暖的鼻子抱着你入睡
no warm, soft, caressin' trunk to snuzzle into.
你们会喜欢这种孤单吗...
How would you like to be left out alone...
就在寒冷无情的夜里独处
in a cold, cruel, heartless world
你们知道为什么会这样吗? 你们知道吗?
And why? I ask ya, why?
他只是长了一对大耳朵 大家就叫他怪物
Just because he's got those big ears, they call him a freak.
成为马戏团里的笑柄!
The laughingstock of the circus.
当它妈妈要保护它的时候...
Then when his mother tried to protect him...
马戏团还把她锁起来
they threw her into the clink.
甚至他们把它当小丑一样对待!
And on top of that, they made him a clown!
他好可怜喔
Socially, he's washed up.
你们这些冷血动物 嘲笑它对你们有什么好处?
Ah, but what's the use of talkin' to you coldhearted birds?
来吧 开玩笑吧!
Go ahead. Have your fun.
耻笑他啊! 用脚去踢他!
Laugh at him. Kick him, now that he's down.
继续!
Go on!
我们才不在乎呢!
We don't care.
走吧 Dumbo!
Come on, Dumbo.
兄弟 等一下…
Hey, brother, w-w-wait a minute.
我们并不是你们想象的那样
Uh, don't go away feelin' like that.
我们并没有看轻你们啊
We done seen the light.
你们两位都很好
You boys is okay.
拜托 你们已经欺负够他了
Please, you've done enough.
但是我们都很想让你快乐 你们说对不对啊?
Well, but we're all fixin' to help you. Uh, ain't that the truth, boys?
- 对啊 对 - 是这样的
- Well, it sure is. - Uh, yeah, that... You're right.
你想让大象飞 是不是?
You wanna make the elephant fly, don't ya?
那么你就要用到很多的学问 你知道从心理学上来讲
Well, you gotta use a lot of' choplogic. You know, psychology.
那你就要这样啊…
Now, here's what you do. First, you, uh...
首先 这样...
Uh, bu...
然后 紧跟着 这样
And then, right after that, you, uh...
用这神奇的羽毛 懂不懂啊?
Use the magic feather. Catch on?
神奇的羽毛?
The magic feather?
对了 我有了!
Yeah, I gotcha.
Dumbo 看这! 我得到了!
Dumbo! Look! Have I got it!
神奇的羽毛! 现在你就可以飞了
The magic feather! Now you can fly!
快点啊 Dumbo 快点
Let's go. Let's go.
快点 Dumbo
Heave ho. Heave ho.Let's go, Dumbo.
- 来吧 Dumbo - 快点
- Let's go. Let's go. - Come on now.
来吧 上下的摆动! 摆动啊快点
- Up, down. Up, down. - Heave ho.
One,two, One,two. One,two. Heave ho.
快点 再快点 速度再快点就可以飞了
Faster, faster. Get up flyin' speed.
用你的腿 摆动你的耳朵
Retract your landing gear. Raise your fuselage.
算了
Take off.
我看是没有用的 Dumbo
Aw, it's no use, Dumbo.
我想 它只不过是一头普通大象而已
I guess it's just another one of their... Look!
快看 要飞了
Hot diggity! You're flyin'.
哇 你在飞了 Dumbo!  你在飞了
You're flyin'!
哇 它飞得象支鹰!
Uh, why, he flies just like a eagle.
比飞机还棒呢!
That's better than a airplane.
嗯  我从没见过
Brother, now I've seen everything.
我不会对这些惊讶
But I be done seen about everything
至到我见到大象会飞
When I see a elephant fly
有翅膀的大象
With the wind.
至到我见到大象在
When I see a elephant
飞
Fly
Dumbo…我就知道你会成功哎
Dumbo, I knew you could do it!
我们还要到大城市去表演
Wait'll we get to the big town.
对他们来说 这绝对是个大大的惊喜
Boy, them city folks is sure in for a surprise.
穷孩子
Poor baby! Whoo!
- 来 跳下去! 赶快跳下去! - 我们帮你
- Come on! Jump! Come on! - We'll save ya.
- 赶紧! - 我们帮你!
- Hurry up! - We'll save ya!
- 来吧! 跳! - 来吧!
- Come on! Jump! - Come on!
看看那座房子 Dumbo
Look at that house. Dumbo,
你就站在成功的边缘了
you're standing on the threshold of success.
不要往下看 你会晕头的
Don't look down. It'll make you dizzy.
他们一定会很惊讶的
Boy, are they in for a surprise. Ho-ho.
拿着这些神奇的羽毛 好的
Got the magic feather? Good.
好 起飞!
Okay. Contact!
好了!
Take off!
哦  神奇的羽毛!
Uh-oh. The magic feather!
Dumbo 快点 飞 张开你的耳朵
Dumbo, come on. Fly. Open them ears.
神奇羽毛只是个晃子 你要靠自己
The magic feather was just a gag. You can fly.
你能飞 一定能飞! 飞 张开你的耳朵
Honest, you can. Hurry! Open 'em up!
拜托了!
Please!
我们…我们…我们成功了!
Whee! We did it! We did it!
让我们表演给他们看 Dumbo 俯冲
Let's show 'em, Dumbo. Power dive.
好 现在回头再来一次
Now, loop the loop.
Dumbo! 你创下前所未有的记录!
You're makin' history!
我看过花生跳舞 我听过一大群人的乐队
I've seen a peanut stand heard a rubber band
我看过针眨眼
I've seen a needle that winked its eye
这些都不足以
But I be done seen
让我惊讶
About everything
至到我看见大象在飞
When I see an elephant fly
至到我看见   看见
- Oh, my - When I see
我看见
When I see
看见大象在飞
When I see an elephant fly
- 看啦 - 当我看见大象在飞
- Mmm, look at him go! - When I see an elephant fly
- 我就知道 - 耶!
- Happy landin', son. - Yippee!
当我看见大象在飞
When I see a elephant fly
我多想有它的亲笔签名呀
I wish I'd have got his autograph.
嗨 我有它的签名!
Oh, man, I got his autograph.
再见了 好小伙!
Well, so long, glamour boy!